groundtradesxchange.com 2010-06-22

# Ground Trades Xchange | Privacy Policy

**What Personally Identifiable Information Is Collected?** User profile information such as geographic area, IP address and email address is collected from each registered user. Additional email addresses may be collected from those who choose to register as Gold Oak members. If paying by mail, business mailing address may also be collected. Non-registered visitors to the site have their IP addresses collected.

**Are Other Parties Collecting The Information?** In order to serve geospecific advertising, some of our advertising partners may collect IP addresses in order to best serve relevant ads. No additional information about our members is made available to third parties without the prior approval of the member.

We do not control how these third parties use such information, but we do ask them to disclose how they use personal information provided to them from Visitors and Authorized Customers. 

**How does the Site use Personally Identifiable Information?** We use _Personally Identifiable Information_ to help us customize the Site and to make appropriate service offerings. 

We may email Visitors about information related to the subject matter of the Site, but only if those visitors have provided contact information. 

We may also use _Personally Identifiable Information_ to contact Visitors _in response_ to specific inquiries, or to provide requested information.

**With whom may the information may be shared?** Personally Identifiable Information about members may be shared with moderator staff of the Site. 

We may share aggregated information about our Visitors, including the demographics of our Visitors, with our affiliated agencies and third party vendors. 

We also offer the opportunity to opt out of receiving information or being contacted by us or by any agency acting on our behalf.

**How is Personally Identifiable Information Stored?** If and when _Personally Identifiable Information_ collected by GroundTradesXchange.com is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties or employees of GroundTradesXchange.com except for use as indicated above. 

**What Choices Are Available To Visitors Regarding Collection, Use And Distribution Of The Information?** Visitors may opt out of receiving unsolicited information from or being contacted by us and/or our vendors and affiliated agencies by responding to emails as instructed, or by contacting us using our [Contact Form](http://www.groundtradesxchange.com/contact/contact.htm).

**Are Cookies Used On The Site?** Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. We use Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and their use of the site. We also use Cookies for security purposes.

**How Does GroundTradesXchange.com Use Login Information?** GroundTradesXchange.com uses login information, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, ISP's, and browser types, to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user's movement and use, and gather broad demographic information.

**When Is There Disclosure Of Personally Identifiable Information?** To Comply with law, we will disclose Personally Identifiable Information in order to comply with a court order or subpoena or a request from a law enforcement agency to release information. 

We will also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when reasonably necessary to protect the safety of our Visitors and Members.

**How Does The Site Keep Personally Identifiable Information Secure?** The Personally Identifiable Information of our Visitors is only accessible to a limited number of qualified staff who are given a password in order to gain access to the information. 

While we take commercially reasonable measures to maintain a secure site, electronic communications and databases are subject to errors, tampering and break-ins, and we cannot guarantee or warrant that such events will not take place and we will not be liable to Visitors or Members for any such occurrences. 

**What Happens If The Privacy Policy Changes?** We will let our Visitors and Members know about changes to our privacy policy by posting such changes on the Site. 

However, if we change our privacy policy in a manner that might cause disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information that a Visitor or Member has previously requested not be disclosed, we will contact such Visitor or Authorized Customer to allow such Visitor or Authorized Customer to prevent such disclosure.

**What Happens To Privacy When A Visitor Links To Another Site?** This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site not under our control. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.
